I'll take point up ahead. Stay here.
여기서 기다려, 내가 가볼게
Very well.
알았어
Yuito.
유이토
Luka, and everyone.
루카
How do you feel afterward?
그 뒤로 몸은 좀 어때?
I don't think my memory is breaking off again.
기억이… 끊기거나 하지는 않아
Should anything goes wrong,
혹시라도 이상이 있으면
I still have this.
이게 있으니까…
That thing feels scary.
살짝… 무서워…
It was supposed to be a drug developed by the OSF hospital.
분명 토벌군병원에서 준 약인데…
They just left it in an underground tunnel.
폐기된 지하 궤도에 떨어져 있었어
Could it be some kind of drug?
무슨 약일까
Unless there is a severe episode,
심한 발작 증세가 없다면
it's best not to take it.
먹지 않는 게 좋을 것 같아
Okay, very well.
그래, 그래야겠어
It certainly around here somewhere.
맞아, 바로 이 근처야
Some OSF soldiers who defected to the Seiran Garrison
바로 이 근처에서 세이란에
were spotted in this area.
합세해 군 이탈하는 토벌군을 목격했지
What were doing in this place?
대체 이 근처에서 뭘 했을까…
SCARLET NEXUS
"스칼렛넥서"
♫A crime in reality♫
현실의 Crimｅ
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven's sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
거짓을 받아들여
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
영원한 환상은 점점 사라져가
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
결코 완벽하지 않아 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
뒤돌아 걸어오는 소녀는
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
순간 이 세상에 기적을 남겨
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
최고의 게임을 찾았어
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I've never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
난 언제부터 이런 세상이 질렸던 걸까
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won't be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
더는 해치고 싶지 않기에 나를 희생해
THE DUBIOUS AMPOULE
(수상한 특효약)
There is no one nearby.
근처에… 아무도 없어
Could the report
탈영병이 근처에 있다는 거
actually be misinformation?
혹시 잘못된 정보 아니야?
Let's look around for a little while.
더 찾아보자
This is the only mission we can carry out for the moment.
지금은 이 임무를 수행할 수밖에 없어
He's right. Before we could determine what's the next step to take...
그래, 그다음 어떻게 할지 결정하기 전에…
I'm taking action to correct New Himuka government's misconduct.
난 뉴히무카 정부를 바로잡기 위해 이러는 거다
What do you mean by that?
그게 무슨 말이에요?
At some point in our career, Karen and I became comrades who shared the same goal.
나와 카렌은 언젠가부터 목표가 같았다
While I was investigating the cause of my late fiancee’s metamorphosis,
내 약혼녀 앨리스가 괴이로 변한 원인을 찾던 중
I discovered their rehabilitation program and metamorphosis experiments.
인격 교정과 변이 실험에 대한 정보를 손에 넣었지
We decided to change this nation from within,
그래서 중앙 정부와 제일 가까운 우리가
given we were in the inner circle.
이 나라를 변화시킬 거라고 다짐했다
However, Karen wasn't the man
하지만 카렌은…
our superior would approve of.
윗사람들에게 인정받지 못했고
I accepted the orders from our superior
내가 책임지고 상부의 지시를 받아
to reshuffle our ranks.
수하의 토벌군을 동원하게 됐지
Now that Karen is gone,
이제 카렌은 여기 없으니
there is no point for me to keep playing the government's lapdog.
나도 더는 정부의 앞잡이를 연기할 필요가 없어졌다
I will change this twisted nation
난 카렌과 다른 방식으로
with an approach that is different from Karen's.
이 비뚤어진 나라를 되돌려놓을 거다
A different approach...
다른 방법이라면
Major General, what are you planning?
연대장님… 어떻게 하려는 거죠?
The government conducted illegal human experiments
이 나라는 불법적인 인체 실험으로
to increase brain power.
초뇌능력 연구를 강행하고 있다
Our people must know about their misconduct.
이 일은 반드시 세상에 알려져야 한다
The government has been keeping the people in the dark.
국민들은 나라가 뒤에서 몰래 저지른 짓을 모르니까
I doubt disclosing this secret to the world
지금 세상에 공개한다고
could make up for all the horrible things they have done in the past.
국가의 잘못을 바로잡을 수는 없겠지
But at least it should mark the beginning of change.
하지만 적어도 변화시킬 계기 정도는 될 거다
Major General Karen works on the outside,
카렌 연대장님은 외부로부터
while Major General Fubuki works from within.
후부키 연대장님은 내부로부터
You want to change this country by working on both ends.
힘을 합쳐 나라를 바로잡는 거군요
Yes, that's our intention.
그래, 네 말이 맞아
Major General Fubuki.
후부키 연대장님
Is there any way I can help?
저도 도움이 될까요?
I'll have a word with my brother.
제가 형에게 잘 말할게요
Please let me talk to him.
부디 허락해주세요
It's best not to do so.
하지 않는게 좋을 것 같아
After all, Chief Sumeragi is your family.
스메라기 본부장님이 네 가족이긴 하지만
But he is also an official.
그래도 정부의 사람이니
But I don't like what they did.
하지만… 난 이런 거 싫단 말이야
Yuito...
유이토…
Naomi and Nagi were...
나오미도… 나기도…
This is unacceptable.
지금 이 상황을 받아들일 수 없어요
Please let me help, Major General Fubuki.
제발 부탁드립니다, 후부키 연대장님
Yuito, you are their captain now.
유이토, 넌 대장이다
When it concerns the country's classified information,
국가 기밀에 손대면
your team will also face punishments.
네 소대원들도 책임을 못 피한다
Do you understand its magnitude?
이 일의 심각성에 대해 생각해봤나?
Then I'll stop being their captain!
그럼 저 대장 안 할래요
That's not going to happen.
그렇게 할 수는 없다
But...
어떻게 이럴 수가…
Well, the only way to work this out is for us to share your ideal.
그럼… 우리 소대원들도 같은 마음으로 임하면 되는 거 아닌가요?
I'm with you on this.
제 생각도 같아요
Me too.
저도요
I feel pity for Naomi.
나오미가… 너무 가여워요
If this is all the government's doing,
만약 이 모든 게 정부와 관련된 거라면
it's unforgivable.
절대 용서할 수 없어요
I could give you a hand.
저도 돕고 싶어요
Everyone...
모두들…
Fine, since you insist on it.
알겠다, 다들 그런 마음이라면
I'll help.
내가 협조해주지
Thank you.
감사합니다, 연대장님
But I am in charge of the planning.
다만 대책을 연구할 시간이 필요하다
Until then, carry out the missions you are given.
그때까지 일단 정부에서 내려준 임무를
Okay?
집행할 수 있겠나?
The new safety measures for Arahabaki.
그렇군, 새로운 아라하바키 안전조치 계획이라
We can't afford another Suoh incident.
스오 사건이 또 다시 반복되는 건 원치 않습니다
Hence, I plan to enter Arahabaki's secure site.
그래서 제어층에 진입해 실제로 상황을 확인하고 싶습니다
Very well.
좋아
I'll inform the control center to let you access it.
일단 중앙 제어실에 통행할 수 있도록 통보하지
Thank you, Chief.
감사합니다, 본부장님
They are here! Above us, at 12 o'clock!
상방 열두 시 방향이야
Monsters, we're not here for you.
네 놈들을 찾으러 온 게 아니다
Yuito!
유이토
Yuito, are you all right?
유이토, 괜찮아?
Your brain wave is not normal.
너 뇌파에 이상이 생겼어
Stop using your power.
초뇌능력 사용하지 마
Yuito!
유이토
Are you all right?
괜찮은 거야?
Helping, thank you, out.
시에니 기오
What?
뭐?
Fine, am, I.
오즈호 매 나
Yuito, what's wrong?
유이토, 너 왜 그래?
I can't talk.
말이 안 나와
Happened, what?
나가 기타…
Are you all right?
괜찮은 거야?
Take him somewhere safe!
얼른 다른 곳으로 데려가
Hang in there.
조금만 힘내
Sit here for now.
일단 여기서 기다려
Damn it, my head is splitting.
젠장, 머리가 터지겠어
The Kunad Gate is growing.
쿠나도 게이트 성장률이 증가하고 있습니다
This is...
이건…
What is it?
왜 그래?
It seems like a reaction to its exterior.
아마도… 외부 에너지에 반응하는 듯 합니다
Yuito...
유이토…
Has Naomi replied to you?
나오미한테 아직 응답 없어?
What is this made of?
이거… 어떤 재료로 만들어진 거죠?
Damn it.
젠장
No, I can't use my power.
안돼, 초뇌능력을 사용할 수가 없어
Yuito!
유이토
There is no time to waste!
머뭇거릴 시간이 없어
Tsugumi.
츠구미
I'm checking.
지금 보고 있어
The anomaly is gone.
이상 반응이 사라졌어
That was amazing.
대박인데…
Yuito.
유이토
All stats are normal now.
이제 모든게 정상이야
How do you feel, Yuito?
유이토, 지금은 어때?
I'm fine now.
이제 괜찮아
Thank goodness.
다행이다
I was fine after I took the drug.
그 약이 있어서 다행이야
If the pain wasn't gone, I wouldn't know what to do.
너무 고통스러워서 더는 어쩔 수가 없었어
Indeed.
그래
So can we assume the drug is safe?
그 약… 아무 문제 없는 거 맞겠지?
It has a weird stench. It tasted awful.
이상한 냄새도 나고 먹기 힘들긴 한데
Wait, there is something here.
잠깐만, 뭔가… 있는 것 같아
Wataru, do you detect anything?
와타루, 뭔지 알아낼 수 있어?
The extinction belt above is too thick, I can't capture the reading.
상공 단절지대는 너무 짙어서 목표물 캐치가 안돼
I need more information.
다른 정보도 있으면 알려줘
It looks like a truck.
아마도… 트럭인 것 같아
There are two of them. They are heading to Seiran.
두대가 세이란 방향으로 가고 있어
What's the matter?
왜 그래?
I might be mistaken.
내가 잘못 본 거겠지?
I have the image now.
캐치했어
These are trucks from Seiran Garrison.
이건… 세이란군의 화물운송차잖아
I think they came from Togetsu.
토게츠에서 온 것 같아
Togetsu?
토게츠?
I heard it was a city founded by people who worship the moon.
달을 신앙하는 사람들이 만든 도시일걸
They became a tiny autonomous country after their independence.
맞아, 종교 자치구로 독립했어
Kagero.
카게로
I see. Kagero's hometown was Togetsu.
맞네, 카게로 고향이 토게츠였지
In any case,
어쨌거나
the target we've been looking for has shown up.
우리가 찾던 목표물이 드디어 나타났군
Are those the trucks we saw?
저 두대 맞아?
I'll check them out.
내가 가볼게
I can't get any information on the building.
이 건축물에 대한 정보가 하나도 없어
What is this place?
이건 대체 뭐지?
This place is fairly remote.
인적이 드문 곳에 지었으니
Could it be a Seiran facility?
혹시 세이란의 시설 아니야?
It gives me the creep.
분위기가 괴상해
Wait. Luka found something bad.
잠깐, 루카가 심상치 않은 물건을 발견했어
Something bad?
심상치 않은 물건?
I know what those trucks were transporting.
저 화물차에 대체 뭘 실었는지 알아냈어
No way.
아니지?
There are similar items on the truck.
화물차에 이런 박스가 엄청 많아
So I wasn't mistaken.
내가 잘못 본 게 아니었어…
What is going on now?
이게 다 뭐야?
Okay, let's go.
좋아, 가자
Hey!
당신들…
Well?
어때?
I got it.
찾았어
This place is...
여기는…
Is this some kind of production line?
뭘 생산하는 곳이지?
It's the same item transported by the trucks.
안에 들어있는 게 아까와 같은 거야?
So these are all...
이게 전부…
These are all human brains.
전부 사람의 뇌라고?
What exactly is this place?
대체 뭐하는 곳이지?
Are they processing human brains?
사람의 뇌를… 가공하는 건가?
But what is their motive?
뭘 만들려고 이렇게 하는 거지?
This stench feels familiar.
이거 어디서 맡아본 냄새인데
The stench? It does stink in here.
냄새가 심하긴 해… 추잡한 냄새
Could it be...
설마…
Don't tell me...
아니, 이건…
Is Spring Pharmaceuticals making these?
스프링 제약에서 생산한 약이잖아?
Yuito, put yourself together!
유이토, 침착해
It can't be...
설마…
Yuito and his team are here.
유이토가 여기로 왔어
That seems to be the case. Well?
그런 것 같아, 어떻게 할까?
Hey, what are you going to do?
어이, 어떻게 할거냐고
Yuito and the others found out.
유이토가 알아버렸어
If the secret of this facility is known to the world,
이 연구소가 세상에 알려지면
I won't be able to protect my sister.
언니를 보호할 수 없게 돼
Damn it.
젠장
Yuito.
유이토
Kasane?
카사네
I'm sorry, Tsugumi. Things became pretty ugly.
일이 이렇게 돼서 미안, 츠구미
What is this place, Kasane?
카사네, 여기 대체 뭐야?
Didn't you already know the answer?
벌써 답을 찾은 거 아니었어?
This is Spring Pharmaceuticals' Seiran factory.
스프링 제약의 세이란 공장이잖아
More precisely speaking, they are running it with the Seiran government.
정확히 말하면 세이란 정부와 공동으로 경영하는
It's an Other research center.
괴이 연구소라고
Kasane, do you know what kind of research they are conducting here?
카사네, 여기서 어떤 연구를 하는지 알아?
Certainly.
물론이야
What was the ampoule you shot Naomi with
나오미한테 투입한 앰플이
was made of?
어떤 재료로 만들어진 거죠?
Human brains.
사람의 뇌다
Did he say "brains?"
사람의… 뇌라고?
How could you inject my sister with that thing?
언니한테 이딴 약을 투입한 거야?
This research center's goal
이 연구소는
is to defeat New Himuka.
뉴히무카와의 결전을 위해
They are researching on Other weapons.
괴이 병기 연구를 진행중이다
Other weapons...
괴이 병기…
The plan back then
원래 계획은
was to transplant human brains onto Other.
사람의 뇌를 괴이한테 이식하고
Then, we connected the brain of a user with SAS
SAS로 초뇌능력자의 뇌를 연결해
to control it.
제어할 수 있도록 만드는 거였다
But the plan changed. They decided to use suitable candidates by turning them into Other.
그러다가 적응력이 더 빠른 사람으로부터 변한 괴이를 이용하기로 했지
The process requires
그러기 위해 뇌를 진정시킬
the ampoule to sedate the brain.
이런 앰플이 필요했다
If you're planning to use my sister as weapons...
언니를 괴이 병기로 만드는 거라면…
That was only an excuse for my operation in Seiran.
이건 단지 세이란에서 방해받지 않고 일하기 위해 둘러댄 말이다
The actual goal of this facility
사실 이 시설의 진짜 목적은
is to turn Other back to their human form.
변이된 괴이를 인간으로 되돌려놓는 거다
How could you allow this?
이런 짓을 해도 된다고 생각하는 거야?
Please take my life.
제발 날 죽여줘
Kill me!
날 죽여줘
Do it for the sake of this world!
세상을 구하기 위해
Why are you helping them?
이런 짓을 하도록 도와주는 거야?
So it really was you who killed my father.
역시 네가 아빠를…
No!
젠장
Kasane is trying to kill Yuito for real.
카사네는 진짜로 유이토를 죽이려는 거야
It's not just New Himuka,
뉴히무카 뿐만 아니라
even Seiran is full of evil!
세이란도 문제가 많아
They are using human brains to make drugs!
사람의 뇌로 약을 만들었다고
But without the ampoule, I can't save my sister.
그래도 그 앰플이 없으면 언니를 구할 수 없게 돼
Naomi?
나오미?
This discovery is indeed terrible.
너무 화가 나지만
But this drug is without a doubt
이 약이 인정받지 못한다고 해도
needed by some people.
여전히 필요로 하는 사람들이 있어
I must protect my sister.
난… 언니를 지킬 거야
Fall back, Luka!
얼른 철수해, 루카
Arashi, why did you let them go?
아라시, 왜 도망가게 해?
What if the people find out about this place?
여기가 세상에 알려지면 어떡해
Kasane, don't you have any objection regarding the ampoule's ingredient?
카사네, 앰플의 재료에 대해 아무런 의견이 없는 거야?
Kasane isn't ready to make the decision.
카사네, 넌 아직 각오가 안 돼있어
We are just the same as her.
우리도 마찬가지고
We aren't sure if we're really killing Yuito
진짜로 유이토를 죽일 건지
and whether we are siding with Seiran.
그리고 진짜 세이란에 합류할 건지 말이야
Sister...
언니…
I didn't know.
난 몰랐어…
I didn't know the drug was made with human brains.
그 약이 사람의 뇌로 만들어졌다는 거
So you know.
다 들었어?
I heard it.
연구소 사람들이…
I heard the researchers' conversation.
하는 얘기를 들었어
Yuito and the others saw it.
그리고… 유이토한테 발견됐다는 것도…
Sister, calm down.
언니, 일단 진정해
I can't take this anymore!
나 그만할래
Had I known it was human brains,
사람의 뇌인 걸 알았다면
I wouldn't take it!
분명… 거절했을 거야
I don't want that thing in me!
난 그런 약 따위 싫다고
Sister.
언니
Reality is cruel.
현실은 원래 잔혹해
But the ampoule
그래도 앰플의 효과 때문에
gives you the ability to talk to us.
우리랑 대화할 수 있는 거잖아
Yes, you're right.
그래, 맞아
But they are human brains.
하지만 그건 사람의 뇌잖아…
Wouldn't that make me just as terrible as Other?
그럼… 내가 괴이랑 다를게 뭐가 있어?
That's not true!
그런 거 아니야
You are still yourself!
언니는 그냥 언니야
Kasane, thank you.
고마워, 카사네
But, I must tell you the truth.
의기소침한 말이라고 해도 그냥 할래
I'm in great pain.
나 너무 고통스러워
I can't take this anymore.
더 이상은 못 참겠어
At this point,
이런 짓까지 하다니…
I wish I could just die!
나 진짜 살고 싶지 않아
Wait, I'll find a way to make your human again.
잠깐만, 내가 언니를 되돌릴 방법 찾아볼게
So please...
그러니까…
Please don't give up now.
제발 포기하지 말아줘
Sorry, Kasane.
미안해, 카사네
Please leave me alone for now.
나 혼자 좀 내버려둘래?
Sister...
언니…
Thanks, I feel much better now.
고마워, 이제 괜찮아졌어
Don't push yourself too hard.
그래도 너무 무리하지마
You should be more careful.
조심 좀 해
Thank you, everyone.
다들 고마워
We should wait for Major General Fubuki.
일단… 여기서 후부키 연대장님을 기다리자
Did he ask us to come here
우리를 여기로 부른 건
to tell us the next plan of action?
이제 어떻게 해야 하는지 알려주려는 걸까?
That ampoule factory...
그 앰플 제작 공장…
Major General Fubuki is connected to Spring Pharmaceuticals.
후부키 연대장님도 스프링 제약 관계자야
I think he already knew it.
아마도 이미 알고 있었을 것 같아
Wataru told me what happened in Seiran.
세이란 얘기는 와타루한테 들었다
I made a report to the government
우리의 움직임에 영향 주지 않을 내용은
with information that won't hinder our plan.
정부에 보고했다
Are you sure it's all right?
그래도 괜찮은 거예요?
Spring Pharmaceuticals belongs to your family.
스프링 제약은 후부키 연대장님의 본가죠?
That's all the more reason for me to report it.
그렇기에 보고해야지
Exposing my family's dirty little secret
본가의 공장을 고발하는 배신 행위로
will earn me the government's trust.
정부의 믿음을 더 많이 얻을 수 있으니까
The people who suggested for Seiran to build that facility
그리고 세이란에 그 연구소를 만들 것을 건의한 사람이
were Karen and I.
바로 나와 카렌이다
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
운명의 지시 따윈 필요 없어
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
분명 고쳐질 거라 믿으니까
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
앞으로도 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 말이야
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
눈부시게 빛나는 태양이 막을 내리고
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
세상의 끝에서 뭘 기다리고 있는걸까
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
♫Who can shake us♫
누가 우리를 위협해
♫Who can define us♫
누가 우리 대신 결정해
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
이건 우리만의 스토리야
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
네 마음속 미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
THE TRAITOR YUITO
(반역자 유이토)